Contact

8800317147 (Mobile) rajat199292@outlook.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ rajatprakashsingh (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Data Structures

SQL

Python

Languages

English

Hindi

Certifications

Certified Data Scientist

MTA: Database Fundamentals

MTA: Software Development Fundamentals - Certified 2016

Publications

Content Based Image Retrieval

RAJAT PRAKASH SINGH

Data Science | Tableau | ML | SQL Noida

Summary

Experienced Software Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the transportation industry. Skilled in Data structures, Algorithms, R, SQL, ASP.NET, C#, MS-excel, Tortoise SVN, Project Management. Strong business development professional with a Bachelor of Technology (B.Tech.) focused in Computer Science from Greater Noida Institute of Technology.

Experience

Hitachi Rail
Functional Eng
April 2019 - Present (2 years 11 months)
Noida Area, India

ajeevitech Software Developer May 2018 - April 2019 (1 year) Noida Area, India

CADDSOFT

Software Developer September 2017 - December 2017 (4 months) New Delhi Area, India

ajeevitech

1 year 4 months

Software Engineer August 2016 - September 2017 (1 year 2 months) New Delhi Area, India

Trainee
June 2016 - July 2016 (2 months)
New Delhi Area, India

IntelliRise Tech Solution
.NET DEVELOPER(INTERN)
March 2015 - April 2016 (1 year 2 months)

Greater Noida

Education

Great Learning

Post Graduate Program in Data Science and Business Analytics, Data Science and Business Analytics · (June 2021 - March 2022)

DataTrained

Full Stack Development BootCamp, web Development · (August 2020 - August 2021)

Greater Noida Institute of Technology(Gniot)

Bachelor of Technology (B.Tech.), Computer Science · (June 2012 - 2016)